

SUMMARY

I am a financial reporter turned UX designer with 1 year of visual and UX design, 4 years of data analysis, and 5 years of self-taught web design (HTML/CSS) experience. I use research analysis, visuals, and design feedback to create functional and appealing products.

WORK EXPERIENCE

CHRISTINA LU

PRODUCTION DESIGNER (FREELANCE) // NOVEMBER 2019

Worked on a visual design concept for a client to reflect an updated professional/medicinal page of the website while adding in the content provided in a way that is easy to digest as a reader.

PIONEER SQUARE ADVISORS

SENIOR FINANCIAL REPORTING ASSOCIATE // JANUARY 2019 - PRESENT

Effectively communicates and collaborates with internal, external, and cross-functional teams to handle client obligations resulting in happy clients. Solves clients' problems by creating custom data reports with data displayed in a way that is intuitive for the client to understand.

FINANCIAL REPORTING ASSOCIATE // OCTOBER 2016 - DECEMBER 2018

Updated various accounting systems and reports simultaneously to complete projects and tasks by their respective deadlines using an agile iterative process. Handled transactions and sensitive data with care by documenting complex workflow.

BLOC

UX DESIGN APPRENTICESHIP // AUGUST 2018 - JUNE 2019

Applied an end to end product design process to build desktop and mobile designs using research data, product strategy, iterative design, and testing to provide clear solutions to pain points. Met with a senior level designer weekly to get current design critiques and use feedback necessary for future iterations.

EDUCATION

LEARNUI.DESIGN

UI DESIGN // NOVEMBER 2019 - PRESENT

BLOC

UX DESIGN // AUGUST 2018 - JUNE 2019

CALIFORNIA STATE UNIVERSITY, SACRAMENTO

B.S. BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION (FINANCE) // AUGUST 2010 - MAY 2015

SKILLS

UX Design Mockups
UI Design User Testing
Web and Mobile Design Prototypes
Responsive Design A/B Testing
User Flows Communication
Storyboards

Wireframes

TOOLS

Figma Sketch InVision Photoshop HTML CSS

Maze

UsabilityHub Abstract Zeplin